Guide to the Global Fund for Women Records SC0671
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2002-203
  - GFW - Catalog (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Company Catalog (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Tribune Center (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Catalog Ideas (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Joan Lamb Interiors (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Fiscal Agency, General Information (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Iceland Conference (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Company Catalog (Box 10)
  - Microloan Demonstration Program Request for Proposal Fiscal Year 1993 (Box 10)
  - An International Project on Woman and Violence - Proposal (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Anti. V. $ (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Program on Violence Against Women, 1990-91 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Southern Africa Fund for Women Johannesburg Meeting (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Johannesburg Meeting continued (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Johannesburg Meeting Misc./Report/Notes (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Terry Mandel (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Catalog Communications (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Seventh Generation (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports 1989-93 (Box 10)
  - Examples of presentation/meeting notes [large format] (Box 10)
  - Group of folders "materials from the Bill Carpenter Project" (Box 10)
  - Loose materials re UNIFEM meeting (Box 10)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - LEAADD Dinner Event -- June 20, 1995 Anne Speaks (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Phabra Thacker BB Lunch 5/18/95 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Carol Yong BB Lunch 5/10/95 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Women's Health and Population Issue Talk by Anne, Stanfor, 5/4/95 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Professional and Business Women's Conference, May 4, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Council on Foundations Conference Info on AFM's Panel -- May 1,2,3, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - April 18, 1995 talk with Nili Nimrod, Rape Crisis Center Israel (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Marysa Navarro on Panel for Coalition for a Stronger United Nations -- 3/25/95 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - April 12, 1995 -- BB Lunch with Nili Nimrod, Rape Centers, Israel (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Resource Network First Meeting (formerly Bus4Wom) -- 3/30/95 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - "Everywoman's Conference" Seattle, WA -- March 18, 1995 Misti M. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Luchie Ticzon on KPFA for International Women's Day -- 3/8/95 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stina Katchadourian and Misti Mukhopodhya on PEOPLE KCSM TV -- 3/6/95 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - February 26, 1995 -- SGC Tea at Kathleen Bennett (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Women's Int'l Day Event -- Fort Mason March 8, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - February 27, 1995 -- SGC Thank you Dinner (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - February 25, 1995 -- SGC Tea at Shelly Gordon's (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - February 23, 1995 -- SGC/ Diane Wexler Dessert for Low Donors (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Resourceful Women Talk by Anne on Beijing, S.F. -- 2/23/95 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - February 23, 1995 -- BB Lunch with Julie Shaw on her Trip to Central Asia (traf) (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - February 5, 1995 -- Tea at Stina Katchadorian's (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - COF Meeting on Databases at Getty, L.A. -- 2/2 and 2/3/95 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Mairi Dupar's Event 01/27/95 U.S. Student Pugwash (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Anne Speaks at MAD Women Party -- January 25, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Bahai International San Jose Award for Anne -- January 1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Winter Solstice - 1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - November 16, 1994 -- Evening in SF Anne Reports on Cairo (L,RandD) (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - November 14, 1994 -- Mahnaz Afkhami -- Brown Bag Lunch (Refugees) (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - November 10, 1994 -- Misti and Laurie Explain Procedures (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Anne Talks About the Cairo Conference at Adobe Corp. -- November 8, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Anne Speaks to the Sierra Pacific Region of Soroptomists -- 10/22/94 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Anne Moderates a Panel at Independent Sector Meeting (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Anne Speaks about Rural Woman at Kellogg Organized Geonomics Inst. Mtg. -- 10/94 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Anne Speaks to Soroptimists Int'l in Cincinnati, OH on 7/4/94 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - SGC Campaign Kickoff FY 8 -- 9/22/95 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - De-Briefing of Cairo Conference -- 10/17/94 Frances, Misti, Anne (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Irene Ortiz Perez of Atabal (Mexico) Brown Bag on Sept. 6 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Zsuzsa Beres Speaks at Mariah Baird's Office on 8/15/94 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Leni Angeles of WRRD and SEAWIN (the Philippines) Does a Brown Bag Lunch -- 7/13/94 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Positive Performer Award INC. Magazine -- May 1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Anne Speaks to General Federation of Women's Clubs -- 6/23/94 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Brown Bag Lunch with Valentina Konstantinova -- June 28, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Marjan Speaks at Joan Meyer's House -- June 14, 94 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Anne is on Panel of Sierra Club -- San Francisco, June 7, 1994 Pub. Sept '94 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Anne Speaks to Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, Women in Business -- May 17, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Professional and Business Women's Conference -- May 12, 1994 San Francisco (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Anne Speaks at World Affairs Council (and KQED) -- 5/25/94 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Beijing Event at the Council on Foundation Conference -- NY 5/3/94 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Jeanne Parrent May 1, 1994 Event for "Wives of Microsoft" Seattle (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Anne Speaks at Univ. of Pittsburgh and Small Gathering -- 4/29/94 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mila Speaks on Panel at Monterey Institute -- 3/18/94 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mila Talks to Women's Group at SLAC -- March 22, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Diane Wexler's Evening w/Anne -- 2/24/94 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Evening at Raquel Newman's with Sister Mary Peter Bruce -- 2/17/94 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Janice Brody's Dinner 1/24/94 with Rita Thapa, Nepal (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Laurie Laird Speaks to Redwood City Rotary, 1/25/94 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Frances Kissling Speaks in DC Mary Ann Organizes -- 1/14/94 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Professional Women Anne's Speech -- 12/9/93 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Winter Solstice Party -- December 21, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - December 2, 1993 Anne Speaks at San Francisco City College (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Interview w/ Anne Voice of America -- November 1993 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Amer. Pub. Health Assoc. SF 10/27 Moderating Panel (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Coeur d'Alene, Idaho Conference 10/30 (10/29-31) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Hemispheres Magazine Article Fall 93 (United Airlines) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - November 3, 1993 Anne Speaks at Evening Event, Devra Breslow home L.A. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Nat'l Network Commercial Real Est. Women -- 9/30-10/2 SF (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - KBHK/Ch. 44/ Susan Sikora Show Taping 9/23 11 am-2 pm (9/26-11 pm) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Chicago Tribune Article(s) 9/18 Meeting w/Sharon Miller (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 9/29/92 Christian Science Monitor Paving a Path for Nigerian Women (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Brown Bay Lunch October 25, 1993 Nelia Sancho, Asian Human Rights (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - October 21, 1993 Washington D.C. Event Around 6th Annual AWID Conference (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rep. on UN Human Rights Conf. San Jose, 9/14 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - World Forum (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Crete Meeting -- Chapter (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Palo Alto Weekly -- Fall Article Interview 10/7 w/Diane Sussman (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Celebration of Culture -- July 17, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Conference of Returned Peace Corps Volunteers -- July 3-4 1993 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Anne Speaks to Mills Women's Leadership Conference, 6/12/93 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Dame Nita Barrow at Esther's House on June 13, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Frieda Kahlo Event -- June 2, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Mailing list requests for GFW fifth year report (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - The Junior League (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Council of Foundations Conference April 26-28 1993 Dallas, Texas (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Union Square Bus. and Prof. Women Talk at Noon -- March 25, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - March 17, 1993 Talk at the Geological Survey Dept. Menlo P. (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Apple Computer Resource Fair -- March 9, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - 3 Events around Int'l Women's Day, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Raqui Newman Evening -- 2/16/93 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Women's Leadership Conf. - 2/13/93 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Diane Wexler Evening -- 2/11/93 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Winter Solstice Party (office) -- December 21, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - November 1991 Washington DC Event around AWID Conference (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Sorpotomists Palo Also Mila's Talk -- November 18, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Bay Area Professional Women Netw Anne's Talk, November 1992 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - October 19, 1992 Event at Judy Breneman's House in Tucson (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - October 15, 1992 City Club Panel Discussion in S.F. (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Thais Corral and Lucie Brown Bags -- 10/92 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - 9/19/92 Junior League Event (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Libby, Marjan and Olga Events - 9 and 10/92 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Resourceful Women Awards -- 1992 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - The 1992 Entrepreneur of the Year Awards, Ernst and Young (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Event at Rosemary Young's House -- 1992 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - June 1, 1992 Brown Bag Lunch Kara Sewale Fiji (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Feminar Tanforan Mall -- 4/25/92 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Northern California Women April 1992 issue April 18th Event (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Council on Foundations April 92 Miami Beach FL -- 4/26-4/29 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - National Network of Women's Funds April 24 and 25 1992 Conference (FL) (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Wilmer Shields Rich Awards (for Annual Reports) (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Apple Technical Women's Conference Feb. '92 (GFW was Recipient) (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - ZsuZsanna Beres Lunch in DC March 25, 92 by Catholics/ free cho (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - March 9, 1992, Lunch with Ninuk Widyantoro at Esther Hewlett's (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - International Women's Day Celebration, March 9, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Inationall Women's Day 1992 March 6, 1992 Luncheon in San Fran (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Brown Bag Lunch for Savane March 3, 1992 DC Group (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Zoya Fanslet/Robin Morgan IWD 92 Univ. of MD -- March 5, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Apple Computer Technical Women's Conference, February 25, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - CHARITech Philanthropy Trade Show February 4, 1992 San Jose (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Stina Reads from her Book at Rosemary Young's House (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Oct. 3, '91 Talk to Bay Area Soc. Responsible Investment Profs. BASRIP (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Asian Women VIA Tour December 4+10 Dinners (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - October 28, 1991 Wine and Cheese with Valentina Konstentinova (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - October 1991 Washington DC Event around the Board Meeting (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - October 1, 1991, Anne Speaks at Haas School of Business, Berkeley (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Eastern Europe Evening, June 21, 1991 at GFW with the Board (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - June 5, 1991 Brown Bag Lunch Lucia Pavia Ticzon (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - May 20, 1991 Brown Bag Lunch with Masotaha Maseko (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - May 15, 1991 Visit of 20 Women from All Around the World at GFW (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - March 15, 1991 Brown Bag Lunch with Marga Buhrig (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - March 14, 1991 Marga Buhrig at World Forum of Silicon Valley (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - World Affairs Council, KQED - March 13, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Feb 24. 1991, Special Gifts Committee Event w/ I. Allende (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Nov. 20, 1990 Sr. Bernard Ncube (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Nov. 7, 1990 Lunch w/ Turkish Women (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Nov. 7, 1990 at the 6th International Women and Health Meeting (Philippines) (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Nov. 1990 Gathering at the 5th Encuentro, Argentina (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Wangari Maathai (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Oct. 25, 1990 Dinner at Esther Hewlett's Home w/ Johnnetta Cole (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - June 25, 1990 Anastasiya Posadskaya (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - June 4, 1990 Rubidia Roque (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - June 3, 1990 4th Interdisciplinary Congress on Women (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - May 18, 1990 Sister Mary John Mananzan (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - March 7, 1990 Screening of The Woman Next Door (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - April 2, 1990 Wine and Cheese in Boston (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Feb. 9, 1990 Dinner at Quadrus (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Dec. 12, 1989 Open House with Afaf Meleis (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - May 24, 1989 Evening at Anne's with Kaval and Price Waterhouse (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - May 24, 1989 Event at Rosemary Young's House (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - C. on Fwd. Conf. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Women, Human Rights and Development 4th IWRAW Seminar -- Vienna, Austria -- February 20-22, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 5th Annual IWRAW Conference -- Jan 21-22, 1989 New York (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - June 25, 1988 -- Board Party at Anne Firth Murray's Home (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Feb. 25, 1988 -- Briefing at Mary Lloyd Estrin's Home (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nov. 5, 1987 -- Briefing at Esther Hewlett's Home (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Oct. 23, 1987 -- Briefing in Washington, D.C. (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2015-060
  - Records
    - Board Meeting, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "By Laws and Personnel Policy", Oct 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Board Meeting (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board Meeting, Oct 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Global Fund for Women Retreat, October 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Grants Committee Meeting, Feb 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting, June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Board Meeting (2 of 2), Oct 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Board Meeting (1 of 2), Oct 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Grants and Governance Committee- Meetings of the Whole, Feb 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Board Meeting (2 of 2), June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Board Meeting (1 of 2), June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Board Meeting, Oct 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors' Handbook, Nov 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Grantmaking Section, Feb 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Board Meeting, June 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Grantmaking Section, Feb 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Grantmaking Section, June 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Sep 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting, Nov 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Board Book, Feb 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Board Book, June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Board Book, Oct 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board Meeting, Feb 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Board Book, May 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Event Invitations (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Network News (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Business for Women Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Brochures, 1988-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 1988, 1988 Jun (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Wingspread Conference - Funding of Women's Activities Globally, March 1988, 1988 Mar (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, March 1988, 1988 Mar (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, November 1988, 1988 Nov (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Grants Awarded Brochures, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, February 1989, 1989 Fec (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Evaluation Information, March 1989, 1989 Mar (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 1989, 1989 Jun (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, October 1989, 1989 Oct (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Advisory Council Brochures, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, February 1990, 1990 Feb (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - First Report - Evaluation Program, April 1990, 1990 Apr (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Second Report - Evaluation Program, August 1990, 1990 Aug (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Training Session Evaluation, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Third Report - Evaluation Program, March 1991, 1991 Mar (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Board Book, June 1991, 1991 Jun (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Fourth Report - Evaluation Program, August 1991, 1991 Aug (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Board Meeting, February 1992, 1992 Feb (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Fifth Report - Evaluation Program, February 1992, 1992 Feb (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Sixth Report - Evaluation Program, September 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - FAQ, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Foundation News, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Seventh Report - Evaluation Program, March 1993, 1993 Mar (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Eighth Report - Evaluation Program, August 1993, 1993 Aug (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Annual Report, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Twelfth Report - Evaluation Program, August 1995, 1995 Aug (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Travel Arrangements (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Africa - Research (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Africa - Research (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, Annotated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Member Funds (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Country Profile Booklet - International Women's Day (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Country Profiles Database (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Alumni Consulting Team (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Africa (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Exempt Organization Annual Information Returns, December 1987, 1987 Dec (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Financial Statements 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Grants/Fundraising, June 1988, 1988 Jun (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Africa, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Washington & Africa, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Financial Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Financial Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Recommendations to Management, June 1989, 1989 Jun (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Country Profiles, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Country Profiles, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Recommendations to Management, June 1990, 1990 Jun (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "Leading the Way Out!" - Anne Murray, May 1991, 1991 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Ending Violence Against Women - A Resource Guide, February 1992, 1992 Feb (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Red Hot Organization, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Grants Awarded, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Conferences, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Report: Southern Africa Women's Gathering, January 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - A Report on the UN World Conference on Human Rights, June 1993, 1993 Jun (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Women Organizing, November 1993, 1993 Nov (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Interview with Anne Firth Murray in Hemispheres, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - The Circle on Sex Trafficking, March 1994, 1994 Mar (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Statement of Functional Expenditures, June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Trip Reports, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Poverty, Women's Rights, and the Global Economy, April 1996, 1996 Apr (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - A Women's Fundraising Book, August 1995, 1995 Aug (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - The United Nation's 4th World Conference on Women and NGO Forum, October 1995 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Interview with Anne Firth Murray, September 1998, 1998 Sept (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Raising our Voices Newsletter, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Consent Docket, June 2006, 2006 Jun (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Consent Docket, December 2006, 2006 Dec (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Consent Docket, March 2007, 2007 Mar (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Human. Right. 2013 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - 25th Anniversary Gala, October 2013, 2013 Oct (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Speeches, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Research Proposal, July 1964, 1964 Jul (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - A Decade of Change - Family Planning Overseas - circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Memorandum on the Environment Program - November 1981, 1981 Nov (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with Arjay Miller, July 1983, 1983 Jul (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Dong Yu-Chang, April 1984, 1984 Apr (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Anne Murray - Speech Notes May 1984, 1984 May (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Environment, July/August 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Articles and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Foundation News, May/June 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Menlo Park - The Country Almanack (Anne Firth Murray), October 7, 1987, 1987 Oct 7 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Articles, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Speeches, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - About the Global Fund for Women, July 1988, 1988 Jul (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Foundation News, November/December 1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "General Support v. Project Support" - Seltzer and Cunningham, December 1988, 1988 Dec (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Articles, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Speeches, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Planned Parenthood Western Region Spring Conference - Reno, April 6, 1989, 1989 Apr 6 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Building Support Among Baby Boomers, August 1989, 1989 Aug (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Anne Firth Murray 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Foundation News, March/April 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Third World Women and Family Planning - Portland Trip, April 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - San Jose Mercury News, September 19, 1990, 1990 Sept 19 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Articles: Anne Murray 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Certificate of Recognition to Anne Firth Murray, October 1991, 1991 Oct (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Women in Philanthropy - Miami, December 1991, 1991 Dec (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Articles 1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Northern California Womean, April 1992, 1992 Apr (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - New Zealand Evening Post - Anne Firth Murray, May 27, 1992, 1992 May 27 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - The Country Almanac, July 8, 1992, 1992 Jul 8 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Southeast Asia Women's Network Meeting - Singapore, August 1992, 1992 Aug (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Giving and Receiving: the President's Statement, September 1992, 1992 Sept (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - San Francisco Sunday Examiner - Anne Firth Murray, September 20, 1992, 1992 Sept 20 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Anne Firth Murray Articles 1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Report: Southern Africa Women's Gathering, January 1993, 1993 Jan (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Foundation News, January/February 1993 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Seventh Annual Stanford Health Policy Forum, February 20, 1993, 1993 Feb 20 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Bridging the Gap between Men and Women, April 1993, 1993 Apr (Box 5, Folder 41)